// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is where supercritical fluid occurs?",
    answer: "A. critical point",
    options: [
      "A. critical point",
      "B. phase change",
      "C. phase diagram",
      "D. triple point"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What are the two intensive properties of matter that will help to determine the phases of matter?",
    answer: "C. pressure and temperature",
    options: [
      "A. density and volume",
      "B. density and pressure",
      "C. pressure and temperature",
      "D. temperature and volume"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which best describes the slope of the solid-liquid boundary of carbon dioxide?",
    answer: "B. a positive slope",
    options: [
      "A. a negative slope",
      "B. a positive slope",
      "C. cannot be determined because carbon dioxide is unstable",
      "D. a positive slope because carbon dioxide shows an unstable property"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What temperature and pressure would show the triple point of carbon dioxide?",
    answer: "C. -57 °C and 5.11 atm",
    options: [
      "A. at 1 °C and 6 atm",
      "B. at 0.01 °C and 0.006 atm",
      "C. -57 °C and 5.11 atm",
      "D. -57.2 °C and 5.2 atm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does the line in the phase diagram represent?",
    answer: "C. boundaries that signifies the dynamic equilibrium between two or three phases",
    options: [
      "A. boiling point and freezing point of a substance",
      "B. melting point and boiling point of a substance",
      "C. boundaries that signify the dynamic equilibrium between two or three phases",
      "D. these are boundaries that would show the sections in any phase diagrams of substances"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the choices is defined as a graph that relates pressure and temperature to the state of matter?",
    answer: "C. phase diagram",
    options: [
      "A. critical point",
      "B. phase change",
      "C. phase diagram",
      "D. triple point"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is where all the phases of matter coexist at equilibrium?",
    answer: "D. triple point",
    options: [
      "A. critical point",
      "B. critical temperature",
      "C. phase change",
      "D. triple point"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What temperature and pressure would show the triple point of water?",
    answer: "B. at 0.01 °C and 0.006 atm",
    options: [
      "A. at 1 °C and 6 atm",
      "B. at 0.01 °C and 0.006 atm",
      "C. -57 °C and 5 atm",
      "D. -57.2 °C and 5.2 atm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What should be done to cause water to change from solid phase to liquid phase at a constant temperature?",
    answer: "B. increase the pressure",
    options: [
      "A. decrease the pressure",
      "B. increase the pressure",
      "C. pressure should be at constant also",
      "D. it cannot be changed"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which best describes the slope of the solid-liquid boundary of water?",
    answer: "A. a negative slope due to its anomalous property",
    options: [
      "A. a negative slope due to its anomalous property",
      "B. a positive slope due to its anomalous property",
      "C. cannot be determined because water is unstable",
      "D. a positive slope because water shows a stable property throughout"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];